Jack got up late this morning.
杰克今天早上起晚了
He ran to the school bus without breakfast.
他没吃早饭就跑向校车
He got to the classroom at eight o'clock.
八点的时候他到了教室
Then he couldn't find his English book.
然后他找不到他的英语书了
His English teacher was very serious.
他的英语老师非常严肃
What should he do?
他该怎么办
Then it was the English class.
然后该上英语课了
Mrs. Brown came in.
布朗太太走了进来
Jack said to her, "I'm so sorry, Mrs. Brown. I can't find my English book."
杰克对她说   真的很对不起   布朗太太   我找不到我的英语书了
Mrs. Brown wasn't angry.
布朗太太没有生气
She took out a book and smiled,
她拿出一本书   微笑道
"Is this your English book? I saw it on the school bus just now.
这是你的英语书吗   我刚才在校车上看到它
What a hard-working boy!"
多用功的男孩啊
Jack's face got red.
杰克的脸红了